LOGAN COLLINS

Senior Full Stack Developer

+1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Brewlabs

= 04/2023 - 03/2024

Phttps://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Created UI kit and unit test script to expedite front-end development for landing pages and on-chain services such as staking
- Developed a bot in Node.js to fetch cryptocurrency assets and price history to show in the TradingView Chart

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

SparkWorld*

= 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Worked in the front-end development team of 5 members to build the company landing page in React
- Led a team of four front-end developers to develop the front-end of NFT Marketplace and Aggregator using the test-driven development approach
- Developed a bot in Golang to get NFT sale data and metadata from other NFT Marketplaces on Avalanche and store them in MongoDB as a subproject of NFT Aggregator
- Developed RESTful APIs in Golang and provided Swagger documentation to get sale data and update transaction history

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

04/2020 - 03/2022

- Collaborated with a designer to create a modern, yet simple user interface for our company's landing page
- Designed and developed Firo Bridge in Golang to synchronize data between the Firo chain and FiroVM chain and store transaction data in PostgreSQL database to enable Smart Contracts on Firo like Ethereum
- Led Asset Tokenizer project and collaborated with Smart Contract engineer to utilize real-estate transactions on chain

Senior Full Stack Developer

Polisport

= 04/2019 - 03/2020

https://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Developed RESTful APIs in Node.js to retrieve products and services data and implemented pixel-perfect frontend in React from Figma Design
- Wrote unit test scripts for the front-end using Mocha and Jest libraries
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and implemented main UI in React and virtual tour in 3d environment using Three.js library

Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

04/2016 - 03/2019

https://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I created smooth and visually appealing user interfaces as a front-end developer
- Designed MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

SUMMARY

A seasoned full-stack developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry. What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA

DePaul Unversity

苗 2012 - 2016 👂 Chicago, IL

3.9 / 4.0

SKILLS

Cloud Services

GCP

Microsoft Azure

AWS

Fronten	ıd			
React	Redux	Next.js	Vue	Lit
Bootstrap 1		wind CSS	Web3	
Backeno	i			
Node.js Express.js Golang				
Larave	<u> </u>			
Languages				
JavaScript TypeScript PHP				
Databas	ses			
Mongo	DB Mys	SQL Po	stgreSQL	
Development & Operations				
Scrum	Agile			
Version Control Systems				
Git	GitHub	GitLab	Bitbucke	t